onpeak.com 2016-11-23

# PRIVACY POLICY

                                      PRIVACY POLICY
Viad Corp and its United States subsidiaries, including Global Experience Specialists
(GES), onPeak, ON Services, a GES Company, Glacier Park, Inc., Alaska Denali Travel
and CATC (collectively, “we” or “us”), respect your privacy and are committed to
protecting it at all times. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, and safeguard
information collected from or through this web site, related blogs and international
websites (collectively, this “Web Site”), our web-based and mobile software applications,
our applications on third party websites, or through email or other electronic messages
that we send to you (collectively, our “Services”). All information collected by us in
connection with the performance of our Services will be governed by this Privacy Policy.
This Privacy Policy will not govern information collected by any third party, including
through any third-party application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be
accessible from our Services.
What Information We Collect:
To provide our users with goods and services, we may, from time to time, request that
you provide us with personal information. We may ask you for additional personal
information if you want to access your assigned account(s) or request goods and/or
services so we can provide you with secure account access or with the requested goods
and/or services. In some instances, we may need to supplement the information you
provided with certain personal information about you obtained from third parties to
process your online transaction.
In particular, we may collect your:
    •   Name
    •   Title
    •   Home Address
    •   Work Address
    •   Home Telephone Number
    •   Work Telephone Number
    •   Personal Email Address
    •   Work Email Address
    •   Work Facsimile Number
    •   Payment Card Information
    •   Financial Account Information
How We Use The Information We Collect:
We use personal information collected during our Services for a variety of purposes. In
particular, we may collect your name, physical address, email address, and/or phone
number to:
    •   better understand how our Web Site and its various features are being used
                                               1

     •   create offerings that meet our customers’ needs
     •   conduct market research
     •   handle and fulfill the transactions you initiate
     •   provide notices about the status of your account
     •   present you with customized and relevant information and offers
     •   notify you about changes to our Services, any products or services we offer or
         provide though our Services, our terms and conditions applicable to the Services,
         or this Privacy Policy
     •   allow you to participate in surveys, access and download materials, and use other
         interactive features on our Services
     •   fulfill other business purposes, such as data analysis, audits, fraud monitoring and
         prevention, developing new products or services, enhancing, improving or
         modifying our Services, identifying usage trends, determining the effectiveness of
         our promotional campaigns, debt collection purposes and operating and
         expanding our business activities
     •   carry out functions we believe to be necessary or appropriate: (a) under applicable
         law, including laws outside your country of residence; (b) to comply with legal
         process; (c) to respond to requests from public and government authorities
         including public and government authorities outside your country of residence; (d)
         to carry out our obligations and enforce our terms and conditions applicable to the
         Services and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes; (e) to
         protect our operations or those of any of our affiliates; (f) to protect our rights,
         privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our affiliates, you or others; (g) to allow
         us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain; and (h)
         to protect against or identify fraudulent transactions
     •   fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it or with your consent
We may use any personal information we collect from you, including your payment card
information and financial account information, to handle and fulfill commercial
transactions you initiate.
Additionally, to better meet your overall needs, we may share your information with our
affiliates who we believe can offer complementary goods and/or services to our
customers or that we believe may be of particular interest to our customers. In some
instances, we may also share this information with carefully selected non-affiliated
companies, such as payment processors, hotels (in the case of onPeak), tradeshow
organizers, exhibitors and attendees (in the case of GES), travel services providers
including third party activities and accommodations (in the case of our various U.S. travel
& hospitality businesses) and collections agencies, to assist us in processing your
transactions to deliver the goods and/or services you request or to obtain payment for
services we provide, and some of those companies may provide transactional services
or send information to you on our behalf. If you are a resident of Canada or a European
Union (EU) member country, or to the extent otherwise required by applicable law, we will
obtain your consent prior to sharing your personal information with any affiliated or non-
affiliated companies. Finally, residents of Canada, EU member countries, and the State
of California are entitled to additional protections with respect to onward transfer of
                                                2

personal information, which are set forth in the “Canadian Privacy Notice (Canadian
Residents Only),” “EU-US Privacy Shield For Non-U.S. Users” and “California Privacy
Notice (Canadian Residents Only)” sections, respectively, of this Privacy Policy.
Tracking Activity On Our Web Site:
In order to make your visit to our Web Site as productive as possible, we track Web Site
activity information, such as pages viewed, the page from which you arrive at our Web
Site, the date and time of your page view(s), your browser type and version, the name of
any files you request, length of visit, and other navigational or technical information,
through the use of cookies, log files, text strings, browser settings, and/or other tracking
technology. However, we want you to know that the tracking technology we use does not
identify any personal information about you. Such technology cannot retrieve data from
your hard drive, pass on computer viruses, or capture any personal information about
you, such as your name, address, phone number, or email address. We only know who
you are if you tell us. You may, however, be asked to provide personal information such
as your name, address, phone number, or email address to us when you register for
online goods and/or services.
Cookies: One way we track activity is by using cookies. A "cookie" is an electronic file that
holds small strings of text. When you visit our Web Site, we send a cookie to your browser
so that we can recognize it when you or another user of your computer return to our Web
Site. We want to recognize your browser so we can make the best use of your time when
visiting our Web Site. For your security, if you are registered for online services and/or
have an account with us, we cannot give you access to your account information on our
Web Site unless your browser is set to accept cookies from us.
Advertising: When you visit our Web Site by clicking on certain banner ads or special
offers on a partner's web site, we track this information to improve navigation and so we
can deliver relevant information to you when you arrive at our Web Site. We also do this
because we want to determine if our ads and special offers are appealing to our users. In
the course of serving our ads to you, a unique third-party cookie may be placed or
recognized on your browser. In addition, we use web beacons, provided by our third-party
ad server, to help manage and optimize our online advertising. These web beacons
enable us to learn which ads we place on third-party sites bring users to our Web Site.
They do not capture or convey any personal or sensitive information about you.
Browser settings: You can adjust many browser preferences so that you are alerted when
a cookie is placed in your browser, or adjust preferences to decline cookies altogether.
Cookies enable you to visit our Web Site without reviewing introductory information. In
addition to allowing us to recognize you, cookies also enable us to securely provide our
registered users with account information.
We will maintain information about you, your assigned account, online account activity,
online goods and/or services requested and your usage of our Web Site to help us
                                              3

administer your online account needs and to continually improve your online experience
by providing you with customized and relevant information and offers.
We do not knowingly solicit data online from or market online to children under the age of
13. If you are a parent or guardian of a child under the age of 13 and believe that personal
information may have been collected about such child, please see How We Use The
Information We Collect and Your Opt-Out Choices, below.
How We Use Your Email Address for Online Accounts:
We recognize that email can be the preferred mode of communication for some of our
Web Site users. If you provide us with your email address when registering for an online
service or product or when accessing your account online, we will use it to contact you
about online goods and/or services for which you have registered or about your account.
We may use your email address to send you the following types of email messages:
•    Service notifications related to your accounts(s)
•    Products or services information
•    Promotional offers or updates about our goods and/or services
•    Email newsletters related to us and our business activities
We do not share your email address with non-affiliated companies for them to market
their products or services directly to you. However, we may partner with selected non-
affiliated companies to offer certain products or services we believe may be of interest to
you.
Ads That Link To Our Web Site:
We may use third parties to place banner ads on other Web Sites and will perform tracking
and reporting activities through use of ad servers. We do not provide ad servers with your
personal information and ad servers do not collect your personal information.
Ad servers are subject to their own privacy policies. If you would like more information
about the privacy policies of these ad servers including information on how to opt-out of
their tracking methods, please click here to visit the Network Advertising Initiative web
site.
How We Safeguard Your Information:
We realize how important security is to you, so we've taken a number of steps to enhance
the protection of personal or confidential information sent to, or from, us over the Internet.
First, we require that a "secure session" be established. This is done any time you supply
or access personal or confidential information in one of our secure online areas. This
technology creates a private conversation that only your computer and our systems can
                                               4

understand, helping to ensure that the transmitted information remains confidential. In
addition, all of our secure sites require that your browser support TLS 1.2 or newer for
communications security over internet connections. Personal information (such as a
credit card number) is transmitted to other websites through the use of Secure Socket
Layer (SSL) encrypted protection.
Second, many areas of the site require the use of a user ID and password as an additional
security measure that helps protect your confidential information. This allows us to verify
who you are, thereby allowing you access to your account information, and preventing
unauthorized access.
Third, in order to bring you the many online goods and/or services offered through our
Web Sites, we work with carefully selected vendors and non-affiliated companies. If we
have to share any personal information with these companies in order to provide a product
or service to you, we take reasonable and appropriate steps to ensure these vendors and
non-affiliated companies protect this information, which may include requiring they
complete questionnaires and/or taking other evaluative measures of their information and
security systems, safeguards, and practices prior to selection as a business partner.
These measures may also include implementing contractual provisions to ensure the
security and confidentiality of your customer information. In some cases, we may also
audit these companies to verify the continued security of their systems and practices.
Lastly, you should be aware that other Internet sites that you link to from our Web Site or
an email from us may contain privacy provisions that differ from the provisions of our
Privacy Policy. To ensure your privacy is protected, we recommend that you review the
privacy policy of other Internet sites you visit.
When you have finished using a secure area of our Web Site, make sure you always click
on the "Log Out" link where and when it appears on the top of every secure page. When
you click on it, no further secure transactions can be conducted without re-entering your
user ID and password. This also helps prevent unauthorized access to your account if
you walk away from your computer.
You should be aware that browser software often "caches" a page as you look at it,
meaning that some pages are saved in your computer's temporary memory. Therefore,
you may find that clicking on your "Back" button shows you a saved version of a previously
viewed page. Caching in no way affects the security of your confidential user ID or
password. If you use a computer in a public place to access your account information,
simply quit/exit the browser software before leaving to minimize the possibility of anyone
else viewing your confidential information.
We will retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes
outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by
law.
                                               5

Your Opt-Out Choices:
We provide users with the opportunity to opt out of receiving email communications from
us at any time. If for any reason you would like to unsubscribe from our communications,
please follow the instructions below:
1. Simply click the Unsubscribe link provided at the bottom of every email you receive.
2. Send us an email at info@viad.com with the word “Unsubscribe” in the subject line.
    To opt out of receiving offers or email newsletters from other companies, follow the
    instructions provided by those companies.
Please be advised that although the withdrawal of your consent will be respected and
processed immediately, it is possible you may receive promotional material that had
already been scheduled prior to receipt of your withdrawal.
EU-US Privacy Shield For Non-U.S. Users:
We are a global company and have facilities and affiliated companies throughout the
world. Please note that we may collect, store and process your personal information in
the United States or in other countries outside of the country where you live. The United
States and/or these countries may not offer the same level of privacy protection for your
personal information as is offered in the country in which you live. To address privacy
concerns, we comply with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the US
Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal
information from European Union member countries. We hereby certify that we adhere
to the Privacy Shield Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer,
Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement and
Liability. If there is any conflict between the policies in this Privacy Policy and the Privacy
Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the
Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification page, please
visit https://www.privacyshield.gov/. We will use our reasonable best efforts to maintain
the security of your personal information, provide opt-in/opt-out notices where personal
information is collected as required, use data in a manner consistent with its original
purpose for collection, and offer mechanisms for you to assist in ensuring your personal
information is accurate and reliable. In the event that we transfer your personal
information or any other data regulated by Privacy Shield to a third party, we could be
liable for any damages resulting from violations of applicable law arising from such
onward transfer, provided that we were responsible for the event giving rise to such
damage.
You have the right to access, correct, or delete your personal information, and you may
also limit our use or disclosure of your personal information, provided that you send us
notice of any such request in an email to info@viad.com or by mail to:
Chief Compliance Officer
Viad Corp
                                                6

1850 N. Central Avenue, Suite 1900
Phoenix, Arizona 85004-4565
In compliance with the EU-US Privacy Shield Principles, we commit to resolve complaints
about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union
citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this Privacy Policy should first contact us
via email at privacy@viad.com, or by writing a letter to us at:
Chief Compliance Officer
Viad Corp
1850 N. Central Avenue, Suite 1900
Phoenix, Arizona 85004-4565
We have further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the US-EU
Privacy Shield Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU
PRIVACY SHIELD, a non-profit alternative dispute resolution provider located in the
United States and operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not
receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily
addressed, please visit the BBB EU PRIVACY SHIELD website at www.bbb.org/EU-
privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/ for more information and to file a complaint. The
enforcement authority having jurisdiction over GES’s compliance with EU Privacy Shield
is the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain limited conditions, individuals may
invoke binding arbitration before the Privacy Shield Panel to be created by the U.S.
Department of Commerce and the European Commission. We may be required, and
therefore reserve the right, to share your personal information in response to lawful
information requests from governmental authorities or as otherwise required by law,
including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. In instances where
we disclose personal information to a third party, or if that information is to be used for a
purpose different than the purpose for which it was originally collected, you may opt-out
of such onward transfer of your personal information by notifying us of your decision by
emailing us at info@viad.com or by writing a letter to us at:
Chief Compliance Officer
Viad Corp
1850 N. Central Avenue, Suite 1900
Phoenix, Arizona 85004-4565
. An opt-in choice will also be provided for sensitive personal information.
By accessing the Website, you are transferring your personal information to the United
States and you consent to that transfer. If you are accessing the Web Site from Asia or
any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and
disclosure, that differ from United States laws, and the country is not a party to US-EU
Privacy Shield, the disclosure of personal information pursuant to this Privacy Policy is at
your own risk. Except as expressly stated in this Privacy Policy, we make no
representation that the practices described in this Privacy Policy are compliant with the
                                              7

laws where you live that apply to the collection, security, use, and disclosure of personal
information.
In the Event of Merger, Sale, or Bankruptcy:
In the event we go through a merger, sale, bankruptcy, or other business transition, we
reserve the right to transfer or assign your information that we have collected as part of
any business transition. In some cases, such as bankruptcy, we may not be able to control
how your personal information is used.
Changes to our Privacy Policy:
We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect your feedback, to implement
changes required by applicable law, or as we may otherwise deem necessary or
appropriate. If there are material changes to this Privacy Policy or in how we use your
personally identifiable information, we will prominently post such changes to the Website
prior to implementing the change. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy
Policy to be informed of how we are protecting your information.
Special Accommodations Privacy Notice (Travel & Recreation Group Customers
Only):
In addition to the information listed in the “What Information We Collect” section of this
Privacy Policy, our travel and hospitality businesses may receive, but do not require you
to disclose, the following information related to requests for special accommodations from
travelers, which may, directly or indirectly, contain sensitive personal information about
you:
    •   Placement in a room nearby or adjoining to the room of another guest
    •   Smoking preference
    •   Special sleeping accommodations
    •   Placement in a wheelchair-accessible room
    •   Dietary preferences or restrictions
At all times, it is your choice whether or not you provide us with the above personal
information.
Canadian Privacy Notice (Canadian Residents Only):
We will comply with applicable Canadian data protection laws, such as the Personal
Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPEDA), Alberta’s Personal
Information Protection Act (PIPA) and other substantially similar Canadian federal and
provincial laws regulating the collection, use and disclosure of personal information. We
will not collect, use or disclose your personal information for any other purpose than those
outlined above, except with your consent. We will respond to your request to access
personal information as promptly as possible.
                                               8

We may collect personal information from you through:
    •   Reservations made at any of our hotels, attractions or other properties
    •   Your participation in loyalty programs
    •   Completed and returned surveys and comment cards
    •   Requests for brochures or information
    •   Your participation in any of our marketing campaigns
    •   Visits to our website, if you voluntarily submit such information
Your name, email address or any other personal information you may have shared, or
choose to share with us in the future, will never be sold, traded, rented, given away or
used for any other purpose than to provide you with the information or services you have
requested or as required by applicable law. At all times, it is your choice whether or not
you provide us with your personal information, and if you do not notify us of your objection
to our use of your information as outlined within this Privacy Policy, we will consider you
to have consented to such continued use.
California Privacy Notice (California Residents Only):
California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our visitors who are California residents to
request and obtain from us, free of charge once per year, certain information regarding
its disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes.
To fulfill the intent of the California law requiring web sites to conspicuously post their
privacy policies, we have included the following summary:
The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to identify the personal information we collect,
describe how you can review and make changes to that personal information, describe
how you can learn about changes to the Privacy Policy, and provide you with a
mechanism to opt-out of certain marketing activities. If you wish to opt out of receiving
solicitations from us, make a request to have your personal information modified or
removed from our systems, or do not want us to share your personal information with
partners for marketing purposes, you can record your preferences by emailing us
at info@viad.com or writing to:
Chief Compliance Officer
Viad Corp
1850 N. Central Avenue, Suite 1900
Phoenix, Arizona 85004-4565
Viad Corp E.U. Affiliates Employee Privacy Notice (E.U. Residents Only):
Viad Corp has further committed to cooperate with E.U. data protection authorities (DPAs) with
regard to unresolved Privacy Shield complaints concerning human resources data transferred
from the E.U. in the context of the employment relationship. European Union citizens employed
by Viad Corp and/or its affiliates with inquiries or complaints regarding this Privacy Policy should
                                                   9

first contact their local Human Resource representative                directly,  or  via  email
at privacy@viad.com, or by writing a letter to us at:
Chief Compliance Officer
Viad Corp
1850 N. Central Avenue, Suite 1900
Phoenix, Arizona 85004-4565
If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us, or if we have not
addressed your complaint to your satisfaction, please contact the E.U. DPAs for more information
or to file a complaint. The services of E.U. DPAs are provided at no cost to you.
Last Updated: November 2016
                                                10
